A Guide to the Nelson A. Rockefeller photographs, Gubernatorial Press Office, Series 3 FA456
Rockefeller Archive Center
- Gubernatorial Press Office, 3; 10.8 Cubic Feet 9 record storage cartons.
  - New York City, 1966 September 17; 1008.15/Roll917A-917H (Box 7)
    - Governor Rockefeller at NY City, Saint Gennaro Festival, and Go Go for Rocky at Rockefeller Center, 1966 September 17
      - Show him with Lefkowitz and Lanigan in Ferrara's Restaurant (195 Grant Street, NY City) (Roll 917F, Frame 10-11)
      - Governor gets gift from Anthony Lepore of Ferrara Confectioners (195 Grant Street, NYC) (Roll 917G, Frame 1)
      - Governor in bake shop of Ferrara's with hat is Sal Candiello - the baker (Roll 917G, Frame 2)
      - the Governor is helping make Zupetta (Roll 917G, Frame 3-4)
      - Rest show Governor at Rock Party at Rockefeller Center Rink (Roll 917G, Frame 5-9)
      - Governor autographs leg cast of Ronald J. Harrigan (Baltimore, M.D.) his face does not show (Roll 917H, Frame 1)
      - Governor as he left party (Roll 917H, Frame 2-6)
  - Red Room. Press Conference, Mr. Wendell, Mr. Hiller, 1966 September 19; 1008.15/1776 - 1008.15/1779 (Box 7)
  - September 19, 1966. Nelson A. Rockefeller, Daniel E. Button, 1966 September 19 1994-1995; 1008.15/1994 - 1008.15/1995 (Box 7)
  - portrait Edward M. M. Warburg, 1966 September 29; 1008.15/1780 (Box 7)
  - "Operation Goodwill," Nelson A. Rockefeller, David Marks, Major Madigan, 1966 September 29; 1008.15/1781 (Box 7)
  - Red Room. Swearing in Ruth Toch, Nelson A. Rockefeller, Lefkowitz, 1966 September 29; 1008.15/1782 - 1008.15/1784 (Box 7)
  - Capitol, Unveiling Harriman Portrait, 1966 December 21; 1008.15/1785 - 1008.15/1786 (Box 7)
  - Capitol, Dedication of Polish Millennium Plaque, Nelson A. Rockefeller, 1966 December 21; 1008.15/1788 - 1008.15/1789 (Box 7)
  - Red Room. Press Conference, Nelson A. Rockefeller, 1966 December 21; 1008.15/1790- 1008.15/1793 (Box 7)
  - St. Catherine's, Albany, Nelson A. Rockefeller, Sister Rose Marie, children, 1966 December 21; 1008.15/1794 - 1008.15/1797 (Box 7)
  - Governor's Mansion, Open House, Nelson A. Rockefeller, Mrs. Nelson A. Rockefeller, 1967 January 1; 1008.15/1798 - 1008.15/1823 (Box 8)
  - Inauguration, 1967 January 2; 1008.15/1824 - 1008.15/1858 (Box 8)
  - Red Room. Swearing in Motor Vehicles Commissioner Tofany, 1967 January 3; 1008.15/1859 - 1008.15/1862 (Box 8)
  - Red Room. Swearing in Aiton Marshall as Executive Secretary, 1967 January 3; 1008.15/1863 - 1008.15/1864 (Box 8)
  - Red Room. Swearing in of Charles Lanigan as Chairman of OPC, 1967 January 3; 1008.15/1865 - 1008.15/1866 (Box 8)
  - Red Room. Swearing in Walter Conlon, Commissioner of Tax, 1967 January 3; 1008.15/1867 - 1008.15/1868 (Box 8)
  - Red Room. Swearing in Commerce Commissioner Peterson, 1967 January 3; 1008.15/1869 - 1008.15/1873 (Box 8)
  - Red Room. Swearing in Superintendent Richard Stewart, 1967 January 3; 1008.15/1874 (Box 8)
  - Opening of Legislature, 1967 January 4; 1008.15/1875 - 1008.15/1890 (Box 8)
  - Capitol, portraits of Governors Dewey and Harriman, 1967 January 9; 1008.15/1891 (Box 8)
  - Red Room. Nelson A. Rockefeller, Ersa Poston, president of the Civil Service Commission, 1967 January 17; 1008.15/1892 - 1008.15/1894 (Box 8)
  - Dewitt Clinton Hotel, NYS. Association for Mental Health, Louis Lefkowitz, Rev. Wheeler, Senator Brydges, Wayne Davis, Alan Miller, Mrs. Metcalf, 1967 January 17; 1008.15/1895 - 1008.15/1899 (Box 8)
  - Albany, Civil Defense Award, C.W. Owens, General Asensio, 1967 January 17; 1008.15/1900 (Box 8)
  - Red Room. Nelson A. Rockefeller, Mike Siglsi, 1967 January 17; 1008.15/1901 (Box 8)
  - Red Room. Nelson A. Rockefeller, Mrs Marshall, 5th grade Altamond students, 1967 January 18; 1008.15/1902 (Box 8)
  - Governors Plaque, Nelson A. Rockefeller, Andrew Smith of General Motors, 1967 January 24; 1008.15/1903 - 1008.15/1909 (Box 8)
  - Red Room. Nelson A. Rockefeller, 25 year plaques, Senator Greenburg, Assemblyman Lama, Arnold Witte from Commerce and Industry, 1967 January 31; 1008.15/1910 - 1008.15/1914 (Box 8)
  - Red Room. Malcolm Wilson, Boy scouts, 1967 February 8; 1008.15/1915 - 1008.15/1924 (Box 8)
  - Red Room. Malcolm Wilson, Boy scouts, 1967 February 8; 1008.15/1925 - 1008.15/1928 (Box 8)
  - Red Room. Nelson A. Rockefeller, Senator Conklin, group, 1967 February 13; 1008.15/1929 (Box 8)
  - Red Room. Nelson A. Rockefeller, Senator Lent, Mayor of Freeport LI, 1967 February 14; 1008.15/1930 (Box 8)
  - Red Room. Nelson A. Rockefeller, General O'Donnell, Senator Brydges, Assemblyman Larry, 1967 February 14; 1008.15/1931 (Box 8)
  - DeWitt Hotel, VFW Dinner, Nelson A. Rockefeller, Mr. Bennett, Fred Stein, John Gaherin, Peter Corson, 1967 February 14; 1008.15/1932 - 1008.15/1933 (Box 8)
  - Red Room. Press Conference Nelson A. Rockefeller, 1967 February 14; 1008.15/1934 - 1008.15/1937 (Box 8)
  - Capitol, Nelson A. Rockefeller, Assemblyman Thyler and family, 1967 February 20; 1008.15/1938 (Box 8)
  - Red Room. Nelson A. Rockefeller, Assemblyman Thyler, Business and professional women's club of New York State, 1967 February 20; 1008.15/1939 - 1008.15/1941 (Box 8)
  - Red Room. Malcolm Wilson, Queens and Nassau County Legionaires, 1967 February 21; 1008.15/1942 - 1008.15/1943 (Box 8)
  - Albany. Delegation from Putnam County, Senator Gordon, Senator Rolison, Nelson A. Rockefeller, Assemblyman Stephens, James Early, Joseph Percacciolo, Adrian Haar, W.H. Glick, Theodore Sillick, Angelo Immorlica, Jeremiah Downey, Donald McNally, Thomas Collins, Ivan Douchkoff, Sherwood Robinson, Ralph Cannizaro, Arthur Kniesch, George Frank, Ronald Peterson, Fergus Reid III, Alexander Aldrich, 1967 February 27; 1008.15/ 1944 (Box 8)
  - Red Room. Nelson A. Rockefeller, Council of Churches, 1967 February 27; 1008.15/1945 - 1008.15/1948 (Box 8)
  - Red Room. Nelson A. Rockefeller, "100 Hour Club", 1967 March; 1008.15/1990 - 1008.15/1992 (Box 8)
  - Nelson A. Rockefeller and Labor Leaders, 1967 March 6; 1008.15/1989 (Box 8)
  - Nelson A. Rockefeller, New York State Labor Leaders, 1967 March 6; 1008.15/1949 - 1008.15/1961 (Box 8)
  - Red Room. Nelson A. Rockefeller receives Red Cross Report, Walter Lincoln, 1967 March 6; 1008.15/1962 (Box 8)
  - Red Room. Nelson A. Rockefeller receives Highway Award, 1967 March 7; 1008.15/1963 - 1008.15/1975 (Box 8)
  - Albany, Edward Unzer skis to work, 1967 March 7; 1008.15/1976 (Box 8)
  - Red Room. Nelson A. Rockefeller, 4H group, 1967 March 7; 1008.15/1977 - 1008.15/1988 (Box 8)
  - Red Room. Foreign Language Week, Nelson A. Rockefeller, Sister Rosaire, Foreign Language students from St. Rose, 1967 March 17; 1008.15/1993 (Box 8)
  - Prisoners Art Exhibit, Nelson A. Rockefeller, Mrs. Nelson A. Rockefeller, 1967 March 20; 1008.15/1997 - 1008.15/2002 (Box 8)
  - Nelson A. Rockefeller. Senator Adams and boys, 1967 March 20; 1008.15/2003 (Box 8)
  - Red Room. Nelson A. Rockefeller signs police pension bill, John Barry, Assemblyman McCartny. Senator Bernie Smith, 1967 March 21; 1008.15/2004 - 1008.15/2006 (Box 8)
  - Red Room. Nelson A. Rockefeller signs bill, Assemblyman Joseph Pesani, Senator Giffreda, 1967 March 22; 1008.15/2007 - 1008.15/2008 (Box 8)
  - Red Room. Nelson A. Rockefeller, Senator Speno, Senator Caemmerer, 1967 March 28; 1008.15/2009 - 1008.15/2011 (Box 8)
  - Nelson A. Rockefeller. Miss New York State, Senator Brydges, 1967 March 29; 1008.15/2012 - 1008.15/2013 (Box 8)
  - Red Room. Nelson A. Rockefeller, Senator Greenburg and group, 1967 March 29; 1008.15/2014 (Box 8)
  - Red Room. Nelson A. Rockefeller, Malcolm Wilson, West Point Cadets, 1967 March 29; 1008.15/2015 - 1008.15/2016 (Box 8)
  - Nelson A. Rockefeller, Bernard Smith, Senator Giufredda, 1967 March 29; 1008.15/2017 (Box 8)
  - Red Room. Nelson A. Rockefeller signing bill, Louis Lefkowitz, 1967 April 1; 1008.15/2018 - 1008.15/2020 (Box 8)
  - Red Room. School funding and the lottery Press Conference, Nelson A. Rockefeller, Earl Brydges, Anthony Travia, Joseph Zaretzki, Moses Weinstein, Perry Duryea, 1967 April 2; 1008.15/2021 (Box 8)
  - Red Room. Nelson A. Rockefeller, students from Brooklyn, 1967 April 4; 1008.15/2022 (Box 8)
  - Red Room. Nelson A. Rockefeller signs bill, 1967 April 10; 1008.15/2023 - 1008.15/2024 (Box 8)
  - Unveiling of plaque for New York State police, 1967 April 18; 1008.15/2025 (Box 8)
  - Records Building Campus Inspection, 1967 April 27; 1008.15/2026 - 1008.15/2050 (Box 8)
  - Red Room. Nelson A. Rockefeller, police residency bill, John Cassese, Malcolm Wilson, Ed Kienan, 1967 April 27; 1008.15/2051 - 1008.15/2052 (Box 8)
  - Red Room. Nelson A. Rockefeller signs highway safety bill, John Burns, Burch McMorran, E. Burton Hughes, Dr. Andrew Fleck, Albert Danzig, William Eckhof, Dr. Warren Knox, Holden Evans. James Honey, Ellis Riker, Dr. Hollis Ingram, Richard Stewart, R. Burdell Bixby, James Allen, Jr., 1967 April 27; 1008.15/2053 (Box 8)
  - Red Room. Nelson A. Rockefeller signs Finger Lakes Region bill, 1967 April 27; 1008.15/2054 (Box 8)
  - Red Room. Nelson A. Rockefeller signs CSEA bill, 1967 April 27; 1008.15/2055 (Box 8)
  - Red Room. Nelson A. Rockefeller, sales tax paperwork bill, John Kingston, Bernard Allanson, Constance Cook, Joseph Shaw, Gwyn Thomas, Joseph Murphy, Welles Gray, 1967 April 27; 1008.15/2056 (Box 8)
  - Red Room. Nelson A. Rockefeller, Mental Hygiene and Psychiatric Aides, Claude Dorson Price, Mary Farrar, 1967 June 6; 1008.15/2057 - 1008.15/2058 (Box 8)
  - Albany, South Mall, Nelson A. Rockefeller, Wallace K. Harrison, 1967 June 15; 1008.15/2059 - 1008.15/2068 (Box 8)
  - Capitol, Nelson A. Rockefeller addresses Botein Committee, 1967 June 21; 1008.15/2069 - 1008.15/2072 (Box 8)
  - Nelson A. Rockefeller attends ground breaking ceremony in Utica, 1967 July 28; 1008.15/2073 - 1008.15/2085 (Box 8)
  - Red Room. Peach Queen, W. Poole, J. Kilgallen, Daleymple, 1967 August 14; 1008.15/2086 (Box 8)
  - Expo 67 New York State Day, 1967 August 28; 1008.15/2087 - 1008.15/2100 (Box 8)
  - Red Room. Swearing in Superintendant Kirwan, Nelson A. Rockefeller, Malcolm Wilson, Louis Lefkowitz, 1967 October 2; 1008.15/2101 - 1008.15/2104 (Box 8)
  - Governor's Mansion, Nelson A. Rockefeller, John Spencer, Frank Simpson, 1967 October 30; 1008.15/2105 - 1008.15/2106 (Box 8)
  - Governor's Mansion, New York State Historic Israel Committee, Nelson A. Rockefeller, Laurance Rockefeller. Conrad L. Foirth, 1967 November 28; 1008.15/2107 - 1008.15/2114 (Box 8)
  - Governor's Mansion, Open House, 1968 January 1; 1008.15/2115 - 1008.15/2134 (Box 8)
  - Albany. Opening of Legislature, 1968 January 3; 1008.15/2135 - 1008.15/2157 (Box 8)
  - Red Room. Swearing in of Ruth Washington as member of the Workmen's Compensation Board, Nelson A. Rockefeller, 1968 January 8; 1008.15/2158 - 1008.15/2160 (Box 8)
  - Red Room. Councilor R.V. Garland, Nelson A. Rockefeller, 1968 January 16; 1008.15/2161 (Box 8)
  - Red Room. Swearing in Sol M. Wachtler, Nelson A. Rockefeller, Malcolm Wilson, Senator Speno, Assemblyman Margiotta, Walter Baker, 1968 January 16; 1008.15/2162 - 1008.15/2163 (Box 8)
  - Red Room. Swearing In Court of Claims judges, Nelson A. Rockefeller, Malcolm Wilson, Eugene Goddard, James Glavin, Milton Alpert, 1968 January 23; 1008.15/2164 - 1008.15/2166 (Box 8)
  - Red Room. Mental Health Group, Nelson A. Rockefeller, 1968 January 23; 1008.15/2167 - 1008.15/2168 (Box 8)
  - Red Room. Department of Agriculture and Markets, Nelson A. Rockefeller, Commissioner Wickham, Don Frickham, Irsa Poston, Anthony Castanzo, 1968 January 29; 1008.15/2169 - 1008.15/2170 (Box 8)
  - Red Room. Retiring Colors of 127th Division, 1968 January 29; 1008.15/2171 - 1008.15/2175 (Box 8)
  - Swearing in of Mrs. Maurice Moore as Chairman of the Board of Trustees, 1968 January 30; 1008.15/2176 - 1008.15/2181 (Box 8)
  - Red Room. Nelson A. Rockefeller, Assemblyman Russo and family, 1968 January 31; 1008.15/2182 (Box 8)
  - Nelson A. Rockefeller, Mayor Lindsay, 1968 February 7; 1008.15/2183 - 1008.15/2184 (Box 8)
  - Governor's Mansion, Business Advisory Committee Luncheon, Nelson A. Rockefeller, 1968 February 13; 1008.15/2185 - 1008.15/2187 (Box 8)
  - Red Room. Nelson A. Rockefeller, Boy scouts, 1968 February 14; 1008.15/2188 - 1008.15/2200 (Box 8)
  - Red Room. Teacher Recognition Day, James Allen, Jr., Mrs. Oscar Willett, Alan Davitt. Larry Ascough, Fred Hammel, 1968 February 20; 1008.15/2201 - 1008.15/2202 (Box 8)
  - Red Room. Red Cross Proclamation Ceremony, Arthur D. Hilliard, Thomas L. Hawkins. Jr., Walter Lincoln, 1968 February 26; 1008.15/2203 - 1008.15/2204 (Box 8)
  - Red Room. Nelson A. Rockefeller addresses Council of Churches, Theodore Conklin, 1968 February 26; 1008.15/2205 - 1008.15/2207 (Box 8)
  - West Point Day Proclamation Ceremony, Nelson A. Rockefeller, Gen. O'Hara, 1968 February 27; 1008.15/2208 - 1008.15/2210 (Box 8)
  - Red Room. 411 Capitol Days, Nelson A. Rockefeller, 1968 March 5; 1008.15/2211 - 1008.15/2212 (Box 8)
  - Nelson A. Rockefeller, Senator Brydges adjust curtains, 1968 March 11; 1008.15/2213 (Box 8)
  - Nelson A. Rockefeller, deed for park to Seaford, Senator Speno, Ralph Caso, 1968 March 11; 1008.15/2214 - 1008.15/2215 (Box 8)
  - Consumer Fraud, Nelson A. Rockefeller, Malcolm Wilson, 1968 March 11; 1008.15/2216 (Box 8)
  - Red Room. Interview with David Frost, 1968 March 29; 1008.15/2217- 1008.15/2218 (Box 8)
  - Red Room. West Point group, Nelson A. Rockefeller, 1968 April 2; 1008.15/2219 - 1008.15/2220 (Box 8)
  - Red Room. Nelson A. Rockefeller signs insurance bill, 1968 April 18; 1008.15/2221 - 1008.15/2248 (Box 8)
  - Red Room. Nelson A. Rockefeller signs Urban Redevelopment bill, Assemblyman Kenneth Brounce, Senator Thompson, Senator Brydges, Senator Garvin, Assemblyman Boyers, Senator Frarner, Assemblyman Hulan Jack, Assemblyman Greco, Assemblyman William Martinez, Assemblyman Chas Rangel, Assemblyman Baker, Senator Barclay, Senator Yauhyki, Senator Robb Garcia, Assemblyman Cohn, Mr Douglass, Senator Lewis, 1968 April 10; 1008.15/2249 - 1008.15/2264 (Box 8)
  - Red Room. Nelson A. Rockefeller, Assemblyman Robert Abrams, 1968 April 11; 1008.15/2265 (Box 8)
  - Red Room. Nelson A. Rockefeller, Handicapped boy scouts, 1968 May 7; 1008.15/2266 (Box 8)
  - Nelson A. Rockefeller. Anderson, Senator Niles, Mr Whiteman, 1968 May 21; 1008.15/2267 (Box 8)
  - Red Room. Signing Ceremony for the Power Bill, Nelson A. Rockefeller, Ernest Acker, John Wilkie, John Geary, Dr. Richard Folsom, William Lyons, Earle Machold, Oliver, 1968 May 21 (Box 8)
  - Townsend. Dana Barnes, Jr., James Fitzpatrick, Dr. John Dunning, Edward Duffy, Harry Slater, 1008.15/2268 (Box 8)
  - Albany, Presidential Election Rally, 1968 June 25; 1008.15/2269 - 1008.15/2270 (Box 8)
  - Dedication of Thousand Island Bridge, 1968 July 11; 1008.15/2271 - 1008.15/2282 (Box 8)
  - Nelson A. Rockefeller. Senator Charles Goodill, 1968 September 10; 1008.15/2283 - 1008.15/2293 (Box 8)
  - Guy A. Graves, Hudson River-Black River Regulating District Check, 1968 October 28; 1008.15/2294 (Box 8)
  - Red Room. Swearing in Neil Moylan, Nelson A. Rockefeller, 1968 December 2; 1008.15/2295 - 1008.15/2300 (Box 8)
  - Red Room. Nelson A. Rockefeller, Commissioner Pierce, Hugh McGaughan, 1968 December 10; 1008.15/2301 - 1008.15/2303 (Box 8)
  - Red Room. T. Norman Hurd, President Service Award, 1968 December 20; 1008.15/3521 - 1008.15/3526 (Box 8)
  - Nelson A. Rockefeller, Robert Balme, President of LCU, 1969 January; 1008.15/3527 - 1008.15/3528 (Box 9)
  - Governor's Press Conference, 1969 January 8; 1008.15/3529 - 1008.15/3531 (Box 9)
  - Ambassador Restaurant, Morton Salt Co., Reception, 1969 January 14; 1008.15/3532 - 1008.15/3535 (Box 9)
  - Red Room. Morton Salt Co., 1008.15/3536 - 1008.15/3547 (Box 9)
  - Capitol, Women's Legislative Forum, Nelson A. Rockefeller, Mrs. Panthen, Mrs. Elliott, Mrs. Goetz. Mrs. Bean, 1969 January 23; 1008.15/3548 - 1008.15/3550 (Box 9)
  - Red Room. Nelson A. Rockefeller, Malcolm Wilson, 1969 February; 1008.15/2590 - 1008.15/2595 (Box 9)
  - Red Room. Nelson A. Rockefeller, Veterans of Foreign Wars, 1969 February 4; 1008.15/3555 - 1008.15/3562 (Box 9)
  - Red Room. Nelson A. Rockefeller, Gen. O'Hara, Rear Admiral Uhanhn, 1969 February 4; 1008.15/3563 (Box 9)
  - Nelson A. Rockefeller at high school, 1969 February 4; 1008.15/3564- 1008.15/3566 (Box 9)
  - Red Room. Nelson A. Rockefeller, Boy Scouts of America, 1969 February 5; 1008.15/3567 - 1008.15/3569 1008.15/2570 - 1008.15/2583 (Box 9)
  - Red Room. Nelson A. Rockefeller, Assemblyman Margiotta and family, 1969 February 18; 1008.15/2585 (Box 9)
  - Red Room. 25 years of service award to Assemblyman Lawrence Murphy and Senator Rosenblatt. Nelson A. Rockefeller, 1969 February 18; 1008.15/2586 - 1008.15/2589 (Box 9)
  - Nelson A. Rockefeller. Harold Uand, George D. Burchell, 1969 March 4; 1008.15/2596 (Box 9)
  - Red Room. Nelson A. Rockefeller. 4-H Groups, 1969 March 4; 1008.15/2597 - 1008.15/2608 (Box 9)
  - Thruway Inn. Nelson A. Rockefeller. Ron Romano, 1969 March 5; 1008.15/2609 - 1008.15/2622 (Box 9)
  - Thruway Inn. Nelson A. Rockefeller, Ron Romano, 1969 March 5; 1008.15/2623 (Box 9)
  - Red Room. First Bill Signed Under Taylor Act, Abe Levine, Al Scaglione, John McCaddin, William Kerwoun, William J. Courlis, Nelson A. Rockefeller, 1969 March 6; 1008.15/2584 (Box 9)
  - Red Room. Nelson A. Rockefeller. Superintendent of the US Military Academy, Gen. Samuel Kastio, Gen. Rodgers, Gen. Jannarone, Col. Stephens, Senator John Hughes, Assemblyman Lawrence Murphy, Robert Baldwin, Congressman John Murhphy, Assemblyman Dan Becke, Assemblyman Gilman, 1969 March 6; 1008.15/2624 - 1008.15/2628 (Box 9)
  - Nelson A. Rockefeller, Chancellors Hall, UPA Group, 1969 March 10; 1008.15/2629 - 1008.15/2637 (Box 9)
  - Red Room. Nelson A. Rockefeller. Senator Bridges and Family Group, 1969 March 17; 1008.15/2638 (Box 9)
  - Red Room. Nelson A. Rockefeller, Genesee County Group, Assemblyman James Emery, 1969 March 17; 1008.15/2639 - 1008.15/2640 (Box 9)
  - Red Room. Nelson A. Rockefeller, American Red Cross Group, Phil Chapman, Michele McCarmick. Arthur Beandoin, 1969 March 18; 1008.15/2641 (Box 9)
  - Red Room. Nelson A. Rockefeller. Campfire Girls, 1969 March 24; 1008.15/2642 (Box 9)
  - Red Room. Nelson A. Rockefeller. Assemblyman Neil Kellerher and Family, 1969 March 24; 1008.15/2643 (Box 9)
  - Prisoners Art Exhibit, Senator Dunne, Senator Bridges, Senator Conklin, 1969 March 24; 1008.15/2644 - 1008.15/2645 (Box 9)
  - Nelson A. Rockefeller, Bishop Francis Mugavero and Group, 1969 March 24; 1008.15/2646 (Box 9)
  - Nelson A. Rockefeller, Award to Senator Don Campbell, 1969 March 25; 1008.15/2647 - 1008.15/2648 (Box 9)
  - Capitol, Nelson A. Rockefeller, Assemblyman Walsh and son, 1969 March 25; 1008.15/2649 (Box 9)
  - NY City, Airport Agreement, Nelson A. Rockefeller, Senator Dominick, Senator Majority Leader Brydges, Speaker Duryea, Jr., Senator Gordon, Assemblyman Cerosky, Assemblyman Levy, William Ronan, Malcolm Wilson, 1969 March 26; 1008.15/2650 (Box 9)
  - Red Room. SUNY General Practitioners Bill, Nelson A. Rockefeller, Dr. John Flynn, Senator William Conklin, Louis Lefkowitz, Assemblywoman Constance Cook, Lawrence Kennedy, 1969 March 26; 1008.15/2651 - 1008.15/2653 (Box 9)
  - Press Release Photo, Baldwin Maull, Chairman of the State Board of Social Welfare, 1969 April 5; 1008.15/2654 (Box 9)
  - Red Room. Appointment of Bernard J. Lasker as member of NY City Port Authority, 1969 April 21; 1008.15/2655 - 1008.15/2656 (Box 9)
  - Red Room. West Point Cadets, Nelson A. Rockefeller, 1969 April 21; 1008.15/2657 - 1008.15/2659 (Box 9)
  - Red Room. Nelson A. Rockefeller, Insurance Bill, Jack Underhill, 1969 April 21; 1008.15/2660 - 1008.15/2670 (Box 9)
  - Governor's Mansion, Press Conference on Art, 1969 April 30; 1008.15/2816 - 1008.15/2818 (Box 9)
  - Red Room. Nelson A. Rockefeller signs School Bill, 1969 April 30; 1008.15/2671 - 1008.15/2673 (Box 9)
  - Red Room. Nelson A. Rockefeller, Senator Staffer, Mt. Marcy Highway Bill, 1969 May 1; 1008.15/2674 (Box 9)
  - Red Room. Nelson A. Rockefeller, Boy Scout Camp Development Fund, 1969 May 1 (Box 9)
  - Red Room. Campus Gun Control Bill, Assemblyman Eugene Levy, Manuel Ramos, Alexander Chananau, Hulan Jack, Constance Cook, Alvin Suchin, Nelson A. Rockefeller, 1969 May 2; 1008.15/2784 - 1008.15/2785 (Box 9)
  - Red Room. Paula J. Mueller, Nelson A. Rockefeller, 1969 May 2; 1008.15/2786 (Box 9)
  - Red Room. Senator Goodman, 4th Platoon Bill, 1969 May 2; 1008.15/2787 - 1008.15/2788 (Box 9)
  - Red Room. State Police Salary Bill, Benjamin Gilman, William Courlis, 1969 May 2; 1008.15/2789 - 1008.15/2791 (Box 9)
  - Red Room. Judge added to City Council in Utica, Assemblyman John Buckly Bill, 1969 May 2; 1008.15/2792 - 1008.15/2793 (Box 9)
  - Red Room. Memphis sesquicentennial medallion, Howard Willey, Robert Huff, Walter Slaughter, 1969 July 22; 1008.15/2794 (Box 9)
  - Capitol steps, Massachusettes Association for Retarded Children, Hank De Grace, John Lopes, Henry Kosior walk across Massachusettes, 1969 July 8; 1008.15/2795 - 1008.15/2796 (Box 9)
  - Nelson A. Rockefeller, Malcolm Wilson meeting with Patrick Moynihan and group, 1969 August 1; 1008.15/2797 (Box 9)
  - Nelson A. Rockefeller with Albany Leaders, 1969 September 12; 1008.15/2798 - 1008.15/2799 (Box 9)
  - Press Conference for Middle Income Housing in Albany, 1969 September 12; 1008.15/2800 - 1008.15/2807 (Box 9)
  - Alton Marshall's Birthday Party, 1969 September 18; 1008.15/2808 - 1008.15/2809 (Box 9)
  - Nelson A. Rockefeller. Garry Hamilton and Beverly Jones, 1969 September 18; 1008.15/2810 (Box 9)
  - Red Room. 40th Anniversary of Department of the Budget, 1969 October 1; 1008.15/2811 - 1008.15/2815 (Box 9)
  - National Christmas Tree for Warren County, Earl Bump, James Donnelly, Robert Muncil, Leslie Hayes, Jr., Walter Grishkot, Jerry Rottingen, Joseph Fiore. Robert Twitchell, Charles Hastings, Robert Hall, 1969 October 1; 1008.15/2819 - 1008.15/2820 (Box 9)
  - L.C.A. Group, 1969 October 1; 1008.15/2821 (Box 9)
  - Nelson A. Rockefeller at Rochester in Flag Ship Motel, 1969 October 21; 1008.15/2822 - 1008.15/2867 (Box 9)
  - Chancellors Hall and State Grange, Nelson A. Rockefeller, 1969 October 28; 1008.15/2868 - 1008.15/2878 (Box 9)
  - Hyatt House Thruway Hotel, NYS. Association of Flousing and Community Renewal, 1969 October 28; 1008.15/2879- 1008.15/2881 (Box 9)
  - Albany. South Mall, Nelson A. Rockefeller, 1969 November 10; 1008.15/2882 - 1008.15/2883 (Box 9)
  - Governor's Mansion, Business Advisory Committee, 1969 November 10; 1008.15/2884 - 1008.15/2886 (Box 9)
  - Red Room. Nelson A. Rockefeller and group, 1969 December 8; 1008.15/2887 (Box 9)
  - Governor's Mansion, Sgt. William Anslow Retirement Party, 1969 December 23; 1008.15/2888 - 1008.15/2892 (Box 9)
  - Mr. Suttny, Charles Rough, Burrough President of Manhattan, 1970 January 6; 1008.15/2893 (Box 9)
  - Nelson A. Rockefeller, George Leombrum, 1970 January 12; 1008.15/2894 (Box 9)
  - Nelson A. Rockefeller, six mayors from six big cities, 1970 January 12; 1008.15/2895 - 1008.15/2896 (Box 9)
  - Red Room. Nelson A. Rockefeller, CSEA Group, 1970 January 13; 1008.15/2897 - 1008.15/2906 (Box 9)
  - Red Room. Nelson A. Rockefeller, CSEA Group, 1970 January 13; 1008.15/2907 - 1008.15/2913 (Box 9)
  - Red Room. First bill signing of 1970 session, Senator Brydges, Assemblyman Steingret, Speaker Durgen, Isaiah Robinson, Joseph Monserrah, Murray Bergtraum. Peter Pisutelli, 1970 January 13; 1008.15/2914 - 1008.15/2915 (Box 9)
  - Nelson A. Rockefeller with Farm Group, Mr. and Mrs. James Earl, Mr. and Mrs. Roger Barber, Mr. and Mrs. Nelson LaRue, Professor Howard Sidney, 1970 January 14; 1008.15/2916 - 1008.15/2919 (Box 9)
  - Nelson A. Rockefeller. Congressman Dan Button, 1970 January 20; 1008.15/2920 (Box 9)